Feelings, feeling, feeling too much, still.
Face 全ては必然 惹かれ合うような出会い 繋がるストーリーで この胸の鼓動 理解できないなら
このまま落ちてゆくだけ さあ選んで すぐなデートを始めましょう
話すたび 触れるたび 笑うたび 目覚めてくこの想い 決して譲れないから
初めて こんなに 素直に そばにいたいと思う
君に出会えたから 信じたいのでたら
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Holy crap!
Is that santofon?
No way.
It can't be.
Where am I?
What is this place?
You!
Answer me.
Where am I?
Oh, I think that, um, well, as far as I know, we're in the Japanese branch of D.E.M. Industries.
I have never heard that name before. Can you also tell me why I have been brought to this strange building?
I can. You were kidnapped by that wizard standing right over there.
Wonderful. This is the first time I've seen such an excellent inversion.
Look, Ellen, that is our dream, our dearest wish.
Now, it's time to work. Someone who is worthy for you to defeat has finally appeared.
My strongest wizard, the moment has come for you to take the head of the treasonous Demon King and lay the foundation for our path.
Yes, the hour is at hand. I'm ready.
Time to die! Time to die!
Time to die!
Oh, mana. Mana Takamiya.
No, not this time. I won't lose to you anymore.
As long as I have the licorice, I cannot be defeated.
Get ready for Blastar!
How tiny!
You've reached your limit. Jessica, the match has been decided. Come quietly.
Mana! Adeptus 2! I'm still right here, Mana! I never liked you, did you know that?
You poor fool. One wrong turn and I would have been like you.
Why? Why did Master Westcott and implementation manager Mathers appoint a little girl like you to such an important post?
Why you? I was definitely better suited to be Adeptus number two. I... I don't understand why they didn't choose me!
Why have you always been like this toward me, Jessica? Why are you so unbelievably hateful and jealous? You go out of your way just to be cruel!
I still respected your loyalty, even though I hated you in return. But that doesn't mean you deserved this.
No one deserves what's happening to you. No one.
Mana!
Do you think mr. Westcott who will acknowledge me now?
One!
it to be my turn this time yeah i know he'll acknowledge you
i hope you're right
isaac westcott you'll pay for this
so
fine get ready go wrong
no
toka no toka i see i suppose you weren't all talk
i won't let you
near her mouth
thanks miku are you all right i am yeah fine but don't think even for a second that i was
trying to save you or anything like that mister just a coincidence
really toka
thank you ellen that was close no problem we can't exactly have you getting killed right
now so tell me what do you think of princess she's grown much stronger than before
my opinion is she's at least a triple a rank really all right then can you still win i'm not sure
nothing that lives on this earth can beat me if i'm at my very best that is which i'm not
i was distracted while defending us earlier when my wound opened up i've been controlling my pain
threshold so i am at a slight disadvantage when facing that spirit
hmm understood it seems we've no choice let us retreat then we still have some time left only if
you're certain it's fine i'm used to waiting it's good enough that we were able to draw out princesses
inversion on top of that we were able to see someone rather unexpected my apologies but you'll have to
excuse us for now let us meet again if you survive takamiya i mean shido itsuka hey hold on a sec
do you know who i am oh no i haven't the foggiest not about shido itsuka anyway hey you bastards are next
oh what the hell is going on i thought you two jerks knew each other besides that she looks super
strong so i don't get why you had to come and save her to begin with i'm so confused right now yeah well
you're not alone i'm not sure what's up either by the way i didn't forget that you got stabbed in the
chest why are you still alive it's uh maybe your secret this is sandalphon i demand that you tell
me why you have that angel toka what happened to you do you not remember who i am toka are you
talking to me shido shido please respond koturi 3d wide range investigation system is back
incoming data from surface all services are normal turning on the image thanks to the building being
blown away the jamming is finally gone what in the world happened in there i don't know i took a
sword to the back then toka turned crazy town out of nowhere was it because of the reverse flow
of spirit power can she be sealed doubtful this is something very different unfortunately i can't
tell you if she can be sealed or not at this point either way a ceiling would be impossible with
toka's feelings for shido right now then what am i supposed to do you'll have to make toka aware of
who you are again if you do that then her happiness levels will go back to normal no pressure bro but
we've got one shot at this of course we do in the end being myself is the only thing i can try
come on toka let's go home and eat if you say sorry right now i'll make all your favorite foods for
breakfast lunch and dinner you talk too much gabriel rondo
michu you're a gross idiot but you still managed to get all the way here for toka's sake so i'm
giving you just one chance to make this right get ready shido
all right now it's go time
how irritating
my you are an insolent one
how dare you try to bind my body know your limits
i never had anything but my songs my music
i had nothing i always believed if i didn't have my voice i was worthless
that nobody and no thing would protect me anymore but honestly i wanted to see it at least once
i wanted to see a person who truly loved another person from the bottom of their heart
if only if only if only i had met you sooner things would have been so different
MIKO
huh what was that
how strange hey yoshino you don't by chance remember why we're here do you
you don't know either somehow i feel kind of strange like my power is slowly being sucked away
that was nothing did you see how we just blew those girls away question is this a serious fight
yoshino yoshinone kaguya yusuru hey so do you maybe know where we are
um master origami what's going on it's shido
yo miku you okay
but why i don't understand i always keep my promises
yeah well so what it doesn't make any sense at all are you trying to tell me that if i ended
up in the same bind as toka you would try to save me too you bet i would
he kept his promise he kept it this man shido itzuka kept his promise
shido
shido shido could she be coming back to her senses
what is this feeling are you trying to trick me human are you very well
my turn i shall crush you nothing will remain but dust and memory
this is bad
now face my paper
shido
also known as the sword of demise
niko go please you have to run away i don't want you to break your promise
save toka i know you can now die
wretch
toka what's going on what's wrong with you
you little impudent
what i'll be right back i'm just gonna go save the princess
keeping my promise
what amazing power please toka stop we have to wake up
toka
Thats
she glosas
listens
the
jumped
and
thought
the
and
but
,
He's gone. He's finally gone.
I'm forever free of that human and his trickery.
And what precisely are you laughing at, servant?
Isn't it a little early to be celebrating your so-called triumph?
Protection. Our foresight is quite admirable, if I do say so myself.
No joke. Thanks. You two were awesome.
Don't worry about it, Shido. It's not like it was hard for us.
Agreement. I am glad you're safe. However...
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
But how? How are you still alive?
To-ka!
Who's... To-ka?
Hey there, To-ka. I'm here to save you.
Disarming yourself. But why?
Because I don't need a sword to do this.
I don't understand. What in the world is this man doing?
He's kissing the enemy on the battlefield.
Why?
This doesn't make sense.
My head is spinning.
Shido!
It feels like my body isn't my own anymore.
Every time I hear that name, I feel weak.
Shido!
But...
It doesn't put me in a bad mood.
Oh...
How could I have forgotten him?
The one who gave me my name.
Shido!
Who turned my existence upside down.
Yeah, that's me.
I'm so sorry.
Shido!
Are you okay?
Somehow.
Yeah, I guess I am.
What about you? Are you feeling okay?
What in the world was that?
That?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Forget it.
It's probably best if I leave that to Reina and Kotori anyway.
In the meantime, welcome back, Toka.
I'm back, Shido. Thank you so much.
The large-scale uprising involving many citizens in Tengu City
that was created with some as-of-yet-unknown hallucinogen
is nearly resolved.
In spite of its scale, there were miraculously no casualties,
and those involved are reportedly...
I'll keep looking.
It seems as though this isn't the right place either.
Good gracious.
Where, oh where, could the captive spirit be?
Oh, yay! You came!
Darling!
Whoa! Who's Darling?
Did you knock a screw loose?
What's going on, Miku?
I thought you hated men.
Well, you're not all men, Darling.
After all, I do kind of owe you my life.
Yeah, is that why you sent me this random letter?
It says you want to talk about something alone, so what is it?
Wow, you work fast.
Mm-mm.
What? How did you do that?
Darling, I didn't know you were so perverted.
No, that's not it.
This is...
I'm just teasing you.
I asked the other girls, and they told me everything, so I knew.
Oh, you mean about sealing your powers?
Mm-mm.
Yeah.
You haven't forgotten what you promised me, have you?
You said to me that you would still listen to me sing if I lost the voice my powers gave me.
And even if everyone else chose to ignore me.
Yeah, I remember.
You're good.
You keep the promises that you make.
You're the only one who's okay with me.
You're the only one that I can really trust.
So even if I've lost the voice that I had, and even if no one bothers to listen to me or my songs anymore,
as long as you're there, that will be enough.
And if that happens well, then I'll sing just for you as long as you want.
Miku.
Shido!
So this is where you've been.
It's getting crazy out there.
I don't know if they're shouting Anko or Encore.
I was sent to get Miku.
Oh, hey, Toka, what's up?
I don't know.
Why don't you try telling me?
Quickly!
Oh, calm down.
There's a reason for this.
Hey, darling.
Yeah?
Dar-what?
Will you please watch my Encore?
Sure.
Hmm?
Thank you all so much.
Tonight I'm going to sing a very special and important song, so I hope you like it.
Well, girls, it looks like she's back.
Singing in the shower
Me believing I am on a stage
Hearing my voice resound in the room
La-la-la, la-la-la, I sing on
Reverb is bouncing off each wall around me
Every echo sounds so special and so astounding
Even though I am happy
I hope that I won't forget how I felt once before
Let me sing you a song
And let's sing along
The greatest gift of all are all the stars up in the sky
Millions sparkle above
And light the night
Thank you so much, everyone out there.
Thank you so much, everyone out there, thank you
Thank you, darling
Thank you so much
I love you
What's darling?
Yes, please, answer
Darling?
Wait, don't tell me this
Speaking of which, Miku called you that earlier, didn't she?
Shido?
We'd like to know what darling means
Well, that's...
Shido?
Confirmation
Shido
Shido?
Oh, no, Shido
What does it mean?
You're so popular, Shido
Mm-mm